Hi, hello, my name is Mukesh and I've been successful in outbound sales for
over four years. I started in a startup,
moved my way up to enterprise sales, and now I'm looking to get back.
Okay? I'm passionate, curious,
and driven, and I'd like to show you a different way to prospect.
Okay, one that's scalable, and, and beats the typical sales team.
So let's begin. AI is everywhere.
Everybody's inbox is full of personalized messages that are really just generic templates
matched with basic data, either from Excel sheets or from a provider.
After they get the basic data, they map them to a chat GPT bot,
and then they get an example of a message over here.
So, yeah, they'll typically get,
Excel sheet, the names,
headline, industry, and then they map it to a outreach message over here.
You can see something similar to this also.
So these are really great, up until this year, because now every big sales
platform like SalesLoft and Apollo are using the same methods to do mass emailing.
And so are your competitors. And  mass outreach,
sorry. So when everybody uses the same data and AI tech,
the real standard for meaningful connection gets a lot higher.
People can spot AI messages easily and start to ignore them a lot quicker.
So how do you really stand out when AI is everywhere and expected?
I just want you to take a look over here.
Look at all these messages. Unlike generic AI,
they mention things like the   prospects' recent activities,
their posts, or comments. Details only a real follower would notice.
And that is real personalization at scale. Most tools just scrape old
profiles, company information, missing the important real-time signals,
like recent posts or updates. And basically what the prospect
is interested in and what they're passionate about online gets missed.
This type of outreach is harder to do. And big companies avoid it because
it's unethical to manipulate data so deeply as a corporation and technically
difficult because scrapers break when LinkedIn changes their site.
You have to be logged in, so you have to have multiple accounts, which
in turn contributes to a lot of downtime. They can't sell a product that
has a lot of downtime. So that's why this approach has a higher barrier
to entry. So enough talking,
let's get into a quick demonstration. I built a quick POC over here
for you to have a better look at it.
Alright, so as you can see, I have,
added some additional columns over here.
5, last 5 posts of the company's LinkedIn,
last 5 posts of the person, and card,
I would say, last comments made by the person.
Okay, I'll go into a quick So this is,
just a quick automation, and what it does is, there are 3 scrapers,
basically 3 robots with different, scripts, scripts,
like, codes, that takes information off of these people.
So we have posts of the company scraping board,
LinkedIn posts of the person, and companies made by the person.
So you'll populate the list over here, with more information.
So yeah, you can see over here.
So this is what the company has posted,
the last 5 posts of the company. It's basically taking information from their
LinkedIn accounts. So whenever they post something,
so this company's name is Luxoff. Okay,
the last 5 posts of the person. And the scenario over here,
to give you a bit of context is, we are an ATS SaaS company,
Applicant Tracking System. So we're selling this software as a service to HR decision
makers. So these are the comments made.
And then you're going to run it through a completion. So basically,
we get all the information we have. All the information from here,
the generic information, as well as the new information,
their posts, their comments. and then we put them together and we use AI
to come up with the most, I would say,
the best way to outreach. Might not be perfect,
but it's a lot better than, you know, just blindly going in and saying,
hello, we sell this. Hi, I know your company does this.
I want to sell you this. It's, it's not as great as something like
this. So let's see our first person, what we have over here first.
His name is Lama Hakeem. And he is in the banking.
So he's in banking. Okay. Here are some of the personalized messages based on
what he has posted. Hi Lama,
I saw that
Annexion is hiring for some exceptional roles across Asia. This made me wonder how
you managed to do that. So yeah, this, this is how typically outreach.
It's questions to the decision maker on what they have done online,
on what they posted and stuff.
So again, a bit of context,
we are, ATS in this scenario,
we are an ATS SaaS company. So
if we go into this, we can see.
I had some, there's a reaction over here.
So this can be two things. We don't have to do reactions,
we can just do whatever he posts or whatever he comments. If he doesn't
have a post or a comment, we can do a bit of reactions also.
So this is very flexible, it's very creative. So yeah,
here's more.
Yeah, it's quite interesting what you can come up with.
So, yeah, in essence, I've developed these AI tools over a year ago that
sales, that top sales platforms are now only starting to adopt.
And as a solo operator, I'm able to move quickly and creatively.
There's actually a ton of, campaigns we could run. A good example would be,
using data found in job postings of a company to uncover the solutions that
the company uses by just looking at the required skills of those job postings.
Okay. And that's actually a good way also. And there's,
there's a lot, as long as there's data, there's a lot of ways to
manipulate it. There's a lot of ways to come up with creative ways of
outreach. So, what I'm trying to say,
anyways, is outreach isn't about sending a lot of,
messages. It's about being relevant and timely.
While others use generic, automated outreach,
I create personalized conversations that prospects actually notice and actually want to reply
to. So this, of course, doesn't replace, relationship building,
or real relationship building, because that's essential in sales.
That's the number one key. But it keeps,
but it helps to keep a strong pipeline of prospects to qualify,
and quickly, and efficient, ah, keeps a strong pipeline of prospects to qualify quickly
and efficiently, which is key in our bound lead generation.
I think that's it. Thank you so much for your time,
and I'll see you next Have a good day.